export const chapter = "Chapter - 5: Nouns: Gender";
export const noOfActivities = 3;

if (localStorage.getItem("activityNumber") == 1) {
  activityData = {
    activity: "Tick the correct option:",
    questions: [
        {
          question:
            "What is the primary purpose of gender in the context of nouns?",
          optionA: "To determine age",
          optionB: "To identify living beings",
          optionC: "To specify the type of noun",
          correctAnswer: "To specify the type of noun",
        },
        {
          question: "Which gender category does a male noun belong to?",
          optionA: "Feminine Gender",
          optionB: "Common Gender",
          optionC: "Masculine Gender",
          correctAnswer: "Masculine Gender",
        },
        {
          question:
            "When a noun can be either male or female and is a living being, it is classified as:",
          optionA: "Common Gender",
          optionB: "Neuter Gender",
          optionC: "Feminine Gender",
          correctAnswer: "Common Gender",
        },
        {
          question: "What is the gender classification for a lifeless object?",
          optionA: "Masculine Gender",
          optionB: "Neuter Gender",
          optionC: "Feminine Gender",
          correctAnswer: "Neuter Gender",
        },
        {
          question:
            "How can Masculine Nouns be transformed into Feminine by adding a suffix?",
          optionA: "By adding ess",
          optionB: "By adding ing",
          optionC: "By adding tion",
          correctAnswer: "By adding ess",
        },
        {
          question:
            "What method involves dropping the last vowel in Masculine Gender and adding ess to transform it into Feminine?",
          optionA: "Suffix addition",
          optionB: "Vowel substitution",
          optionC: "Consonant addition",
          correctAnswer: "Vowel substitution",
        },
        {
          question:
            "When a word is added to a Common Gender noun to transform it into Feminine, what is this method called?",
          optionA: "Addition transformation",
          optionB: "Gender conversion",
          optionC: "Common gender transformation",
          correctAnswer: "Gender conversion",
        },
        {
          question:
            "What is the purpose of using an entirely different word to transform Masculine into Feminine?",
          optionA: "Aesthetic transformation",
          optionB: "Comprehensive conversion",
          optionC: "Radical transformation",
          correctAnswer: "Radical transformation",
        },
        {
          question: "Which gender category does a female noun belong to?",
          optionA: "Feminine Gender",
          optionB: "Common Gender",
          optionC: "Masculine Gender",
          correctAnswer: "Feminine Gender",
        },
        {
          question:
            "In the context of gender transformation, what does adding 'ess' typically indicate?",
          optionA: "Masculine to Feminine transformation",
          optionB: "Neuter to Feminine transformation",
          optionC: "Common to Masculine transformation",
          correctAnswer: "Masculine to Feminine transformation",
        },
      ],
  };
}

if (localStorage.getItem("activityNumber") == 2) {
  activityData = {
    activity: "Fill in the blank with correct option:",
    questions: [
        {
          question:
            "___________ is a word processing application that allows you to create a variety of documents like letters, articles, poems, stories, reports, etc.",
          optionA: "Word",
          optionB: "Excel",
          optionC: "PowerPoint",
          correctAnswer: "Word",
        },
        {
          question:
            "The Quick Access Toolbar in Word contains shortcuts for common commands such as Save, Undo, and ___________.",
          optionA: "Print",
          optionB: "Redo",
          optionC: "Copy",
          correctAnswer: "Redo",
        },
        {
          question:
            "The ruler in Word is located at the ______________ of your document and is used to adjust the document with precision.",
          optionA: "Bottom",
          optionB: "Top and left",
          optionC: "Right",
          correctAnswer: "Top and left",
        },
        {
          question:
            "The document area in Word is a large white blank area used for _____________.",
          optionA: "Formatting text",
          optionB: "Typing text",
          optionC: "Inserting images",
          correctAnswer: "Typing text",
        },
        {
          question:
            "To start a new document in Word, one should select ______________ on the Word start screen.",
          optionA: "Recent document",
          optionB: "Blank document",
          optionC: "Saved document",
          correctAnswer: "Blank document",
        },
        {
          question:
            "To change the location of the insertion point in Word, you can simply click on the location or use _______________.",
          optionA: "Spacebar",
          optionB: "Arrow keys",
          optionC: "Caps Lock",
          correctAnswer: "Arrow keys",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Saving a document is crucial when starting a new document or making changes. In Word, to save a file for the first time, one should click on _______________.",
          optionA: "Save As",
          optionB: "Save option",
          optionC: "Close option",
          correctAnswer: "Save As",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Word offers two ways to save a file: _______________ and Save As.",
          optionA: "Save",
          optionB: "Save and Exit",
          optionC: "Save and Close",
          correctAnswer: "Save",
        },
        {
          question:
            "To open an existing document in Word, one should navigate to backstage view and click on the _______________ option.",
          optionA: "Close",
          optionB: "Print",
          optionC: "Open",
          correctAnswer: "Open",
        },
        {
          question:
            "The Print pane in Word allows users to preview and print a document, accessed by clicking on the _______________ option in the File tab.",
          optionA: "Save",
          optionB: "Print",
          optionC: "Close",
          correctAnswer: "Print",
        },
      ],
  };
}

if (localStorage.getItem("activityNumber") == 3) {
  activityData = {
    activity: "Write 'True' for True and 'False' for False statements:",
    questions: [
        {
          question:
            "Gender categorization of nouns is based on their biological attributes.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "True",
        },
        {
          question: "Common Gender applies only to non-living entities.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "False",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Neuter Gender is used for nouns that can be either male or female.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "False",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Adding 'ess' is a method to transform Masculine Nouns into Feminine.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "True",
        },
        {
          question:
            "The ruler in Word is located at the bottom of the document.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "False",
        },
        {
          question:
            "The Quick Access Toolbar in Word includes shortcuts for common commands like Redo.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "True",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Saving a document for the first time in Word involves clicking on the 'Save' option.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "False",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Word offers only one way to save a file, which is the 'Save' option.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "False",
        },
        {
          question:
            "The Print pane in Word allows users to preview and print a document.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "True",
        },
        {
          question:
            "The Caps Lock key in Word is used to change the font size.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "False",
        },
      ],
  };
}

export var activityData;
